[{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678970279,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":31535,"timeElapsed":103805},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678987597,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":17313,"timeElapsed":121124},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679001878,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":14275,"timeElapsed":135404},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679015737,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":13856,"timeElapsed":149264},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679031282,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":15541,"timeElapsed":164808},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679039132,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":7848,"timeElapsed":172658},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679059298,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":20164,"timeElapsed":192825},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679075394,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":16093,"timeElapsed":208921},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679099060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":23663,"timeElapsed":232587},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679137038,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":35945,"timeElapsed":270564},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679141682,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":4641,"timeElapsed":275209},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679150401,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":8716,"timeElapsed":283928},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679159177,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":8773,"timeElapsed":292704},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679167826,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":8646,"timeElapsed":301353},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679175892,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":8064,"timeElapsed":309419},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679183517,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":7621,"timeElapsed":317044},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679198924,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":15404,"timeElapsed":332451},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679209850,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":10922,"timeElapsed":343377},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679226250,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":14528,"timeElapsed":359777},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679232717,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":6464,"timeElapsed":366244},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679240348,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":7628,"timeElapsed":373875},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679247346,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6996,"timeElapsed":380873},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679255953,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":8605,"timeElapsed":389480},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679262379,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6423,"timeElapsed":395906},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679268786,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":6404,"timeElapsed":402313},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679279062,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":10272,"timeElapsed":412589},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679286554,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":7489,"timeElapsed":420081},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679300796,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":12305,"timeElapsed":434323},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679308796,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":7996,"timeElapsed":442323},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679316986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":8186,"timeElapsed":450513},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679323644,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":6656,"timeElapsed":457171},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679330877,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":7229,"timeElapsed":464404},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679340546,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9665,"timeElapsed":474073},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679344957,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":4408,"timeElapsed":478484},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679351154,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":6193,"timeElapsed":484681},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679360466,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":9310,"timeElapsed":493993},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679369942,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":9473,"timeElapsed":503468},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679384442,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":12750,"timeElapsed":517969},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679390653,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":6208,"timeElapsed":524180},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679397021,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":6362,"timeElapsed":530548},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679404317,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":7291,"timeElapsed":537844},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679410474,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":6154,"timeElapsed":544001},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679414939,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":4463,"timeElapsed":548466},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679421755,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":6813,"timeElapsed":555282},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679430083,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":8326,"timeElapsed":563610},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679438570,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":8485,"timeElapsed":572097},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679459458,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":19152,"timeElapsed":592985},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679464482,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":5021,"timeElapsed":598009},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679472229,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":7744,"timeElapsed":605756},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679477845,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":5612,"timeElapsed":611372},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679484876,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":7027,"timeElapsed":618403},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679490996,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":6116,"timeElapsed":624523},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679497404,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":6405,"timeElapsed":630931},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679508851,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":11442,"timeElapsed":642378},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679515141,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"161","question":"Describe the best friend of one of your parents or siblings.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":6287,"timeElapsed":648668},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679532531,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":15821,"timeElapsed":666058},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679538892,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":6355,"timeElapsed":672419},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679544764,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":5868,"timeElapsed":678291},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679550835,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":6067,"timeElapsed":684362},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679557450,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":6612,"timeElapsed":690977},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679562634,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":5182,"timeElapsed":696161},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679566677,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":4040,"timeElapsed":700204},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679577901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":11220,"timeElapsed":711428},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679583508,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":5603,"timeElapsed":717035},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679595610,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":10343,"timeElapsed":729137},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679600994,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":5381,"timeElapsed":734521},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679607785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":6790,"timeElapsed":741312},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679614493,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":6705,"timeElapsed":748020},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679621786,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":7289,"timeElapsed":755313},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679630077,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8288,"timeElapsed":763603},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679636210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":6129,"timeElapsed":769737},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679642142,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":5929,"timeElapsed":775669},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679651293,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":9148,"timeElapsed":784820},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679658186,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":6888,"timeElapsed":791712},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679672858,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":12817,"timeElapsed":806385},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679677693,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":4831,"timeElapsed":811220},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679684845,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":7148,"timeElapsed":818372},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679691186,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":6338,"timeElapsed":824713},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679700154,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":8966,"timeElapsed":833681},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679705794,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":5638,"timeElapsed":839321},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679711666,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":5870,"timeElapsed":845193},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679721445,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":9775,"timeElapsed":854971},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679729970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":8522,"timeElapsed":863497},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679747203,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":15696,"timeElapsed":880730},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679755774,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":8568,"timeElapsed":889301},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679765813,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":10035,"timeElapsed":899340},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679774069,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":8252,"timeElapsed":907596},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679780299,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":6225,"timeElapsed":913826},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679787595,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":7293,"timeElapsed":921122},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679793755,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":6158,"timeElapsed":927282},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679801629,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":7872,"timeElapsed":935156},{"subjectID":"bfh5qymnl3","prolificID":"6053e01a6a8e8516ba7d47a7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ba27970e0fcd674fd","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679810379,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":8746,"timeElapsed":943906}]